Finding Aid for the Grantland Rice Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Newspaper clippings of poems, articles, and columns by Grantland Rice
  - Index of all poems, articles, and columns by Grantland Rice
    - Locating the Duffer (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - The Lone Exception (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Lonesome for You (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - The Long, Long Trail (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - The Long Tramp (Box 4, Folder 21, Box 6, Folder 32)
    - The Long Watch 5-8, 13 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Look Who's Here (Box 4, Folder 24, Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Looking Ahead (Box 7, Folder 45, Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Looking Back (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Looking Back a Trifle (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Lookin' Backward (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Looking to 1943 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - The Lost Gift (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - The Lost Goddess (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Lost May (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - The Lost Road (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - The Lost Thanksgiving Day (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Lost Trails (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Love and June (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - The Love Sonnets of a Son of Swat (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Loves Day (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - The Lower Strata (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - The Lucky Gent (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - The Lucky Zoo Trainer (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - The Lyrical Game (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Madrigal (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - A Magazine 'Pome' (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - The Main Answer (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - The Main Idea (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - The Main Query (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - The Main Refrain (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - The Main Show in Washington (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - The Main Sport (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - The Main Spot (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - The Major Issue (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - The Major Leaguer's Daughter (Box 4, Folder 7, Box 5, Folder 2)
    - The Major Poison (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - The Major Puzzle (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Making Hay While the Snow Flies (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Making It at Home (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Man of the Hour (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - The Man Who Played with Anson on the Old Chicago Team (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Manhattan vs. Smoky Joe (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Many Moons Ago (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - The March (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - The March of the Human Hace (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Marching Again (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Marching to Georgia (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - A Marine Comes Home (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Marmion and Douglas Up-to-Date (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Marquard's Rebuttal (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Marquard's Soliloquy (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Mary's Possessions (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - The Master Said It (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - The Masterpiece (Box 5, Folder 14, 50)
    - A Matter of Moment (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Maud Muller Sees the Naps (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - May Dusk (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - May Madness (Box 7, Folder 45, Box 8, Folder 15)
    - McGraw's Exhortation to Battle (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - McGraw's Exhortation to His Men in Battle (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Me and My Pal--with the Shaggy Coat (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Meaning Mr. Haughton, Harvard, and Mr. Cobb, Detroit (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - The Measure of a Man (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - The Measure of Dreams (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Medley (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - M'Elveen, the Candy (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - The Melancholy Days (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Melancholy Sights (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Memorial Day, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - A Memorial Day Toast (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Memories and Thanks (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Memory's Land (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Memphis Mangled (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - The Mental vs. the Physical (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Merely a Yearn (Box 6, Folder 5, 6)
    - A Message from a Front Trench (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - A Message from the 'Dream Warden' (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - A Message from the Front Line (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - The Message of the Winds (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Mighty Casey Reincarnated (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Might Have Been (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Mike Murphy (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Missing Faces (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Modern Golf (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - The Modern Methusaleh (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Modern Song of Sports (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Modern Sport (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - The Modern Version (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - The Mogul's Dream (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - The Moral of the Year (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Morale (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - More Lines to John Franklin Baker (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - More of the Same (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - More Philosophy (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - More Sporting Philosophy (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Morning Land (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Moth-Eaten Mottos (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Mother Goose on the Fight (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - "A mother's gift" (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Mr. Adam in Disguise (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Mr. Hurry-up Yost (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Mudville's Fate (Box 4, Folder 6, Box 5, Folder 22)
    - My Choice (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - My Friend 'Trouble' (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - My Lady of Spring (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - The Mystery (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Naps Annex Big Victory (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Naps Revenged on Packing-ton (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Nassau Fish (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - The National Pantheon (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - The National Rubaiyat (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Natural Gas and Its Effects (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - The 'Near' Variety (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Never Again (Box 5, Folder 6, 22)
    - Never Neverland (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - The New Army (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - The New Arrival (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - New College Yell (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - The New Dealer (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - The New Dynasty (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - The New Era (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - The New Generation (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - The New Lochinvar (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - The New Melody (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - The New Method (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - The New Movie Test (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - The New Grder (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - New Recruit Ballads (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - New xRequirements (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - A New Sport Program (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - The New Sporting Season (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - New Uses for the Atom (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - The New Way (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - The New World--Sport's Answer (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - The New World War (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - New Year Resolutions (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - A New Year Tip to Mr. Lajoie (Box 4, Folder 3, Box 5, Folder 16)
    - A New 4ear Wish (Box 6, Folder 33, 52)
    - New Year's Poem (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - The Night (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - The 1917 Color Scheme (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - 1918-1940 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - 1919 Mobilization (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - 1921 in Review (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - 1943 Football Up-to-Date (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - The 1943 Pennant Cruise (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - A 1943 Philosophy (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - 1943 Thanksgiving (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - No Man's Land (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - No 'Nature Faking' (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - "No wonder you can swing" (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Not Knocking, But-- (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Not Knocking--Of Course (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Not This Summer (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Not Yet (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Not Yet--But (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - A Note for the Bewildered (Box 8, Folder 4, 19)
    - 'Nother Fall Note (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Nothing Doing (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Nothing to It (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - November Golf (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - November 9, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - November 10, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Now You Can Weep, My Lady (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Now You've Heard It All (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - The Nugget of Naugatuck (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - A Nursery Ballad of Balldom (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Nursery Jingles Up-to-Date (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Nursery Memories (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - A Nursery Tale Up-to-Date (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - O Blissful Era! (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - O Temporal 0 Mores! (Box 4, Folder 18, Box 7, Folder 32)
    - O Woman with the Hobble Skirt (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - October Fancies (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - October Golf (Box 6, Folder 48, Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Ode to February (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Ode to Gentle Annie (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - "Of all the beautiful" (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Of the Two (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Off in a Bunch (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - The Off-Trail (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - An Off-Trail Thanksgiving (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - The Off-Trail to Christmas (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Offering a Vow (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - "Oft in the chilly night" (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - 0ft in the Stilly Night (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Oh, the Sun Shines Bright (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Old Autumn Ways 4-25 Old Boy Honus (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Old Boys in Has-Been Land Welcome Fitz across the Styx (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Old, But to the Point (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - An Old Competitor Speaks (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Old Comrades (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - The Old Cumberland's Callin' -- 'Come Home' (Box 8, Folder 24, Box 5, Folder 23)
    - The Old Doc (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Old Dreams (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - An Old-Fashioned Tune (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Old Glory (Box 4, Folder 14, 16)
    - The Old grad (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - The Old Grad and Autumn (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - The Old Grad Speaks Again 7-9. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - The Old Grad's Dream (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - The Old Grad's Reaction (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Old Hickory's Friend (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - An Old Love Song (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - The Old Lure (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - 01, Man Lindy (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - The Old Man Speaks (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - An Old Melody Revisited (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Old Nap Tucker (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - The Old, Old Lure (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - The Old, Old Story (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - An Old One, Revamped (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Old Omar Speaks Again (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Old Omar Up-to-Date (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Old Rivals (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - An Old Song (Box 8, Folder 16, 19)
    - The Old Song Returns (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Old Songs Resung (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Old Songs Revised (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - An Old Thanksgiving (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - The Old Third Baseman (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Old-Time Fellow (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Oldtimers (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - The Old-Timer's Dream (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - The Old Typewriter League (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - The Olympic Call (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - On a Rainy Day (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - On Abolishing the Daily Double (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - The On and Off Day (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - On Being Able to Take It (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - On Being Aggressive (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - On Being Prepared (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - On Being Ready (Box 6, Folder 30, Box 7, Folder 46)
    - On Christmas Eve 4-21 (Box 5, Folder 11, Box 7, Folder 46)
    - On Facing Killing Odds (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - On Juvenile Crime and Juvenile Sport (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - On Keeping Cool (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - On Life's Gridiron (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - On Life's Highway (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - On Memory's Wall (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - On the Battle's Eve (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - On the Coaching Lines (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - On the Edge of April 4-29 (Box 5, Folder 2, Box 8, Folder 19)
    - On the Highway (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - On the National Gridiron (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - On the Other Hand 4-23, 25; 5-11; 6-51, 56 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - On the Other Paw (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - On the Quiet (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - On the Return of Big Bill Tilden (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - On the Road (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - On the Road to Man at Play (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - On the Road to Play Croquet (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - On the Road to Rooter's Row (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - On the Sands of Life (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - On the Threshold (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - On the Way (Box 4, Folder 22, Box 5, Folder 4)
    - On Their Shields Our Warriors Return (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - On to Christmas Morning (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Once upon a Time (Box 5, Folder 12, Box 6, Folder 49)
    - 100 Per Cent Hate (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - One of Morgan's 4en (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - One T.R. Cobb (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - The Ones You Miss (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Only a Dream (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Only a Little Way (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - The Only Scotch Game You Can Play (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Open Country (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Open Letter to C. Mack (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Opening Chorus (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - The Opening Overture (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Opposite Winds (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - The Orchard Lanes of Long Ago (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - The Original 'Wondrous Wise' (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - The Other Half (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - The Other Hill (Box 4, Folder 1, Box 5, Folder 22)
    - The Other One (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - The Other Side (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - The Other Side of It (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Other Thrills (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Other Varieties (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Otto's Name Led the Rest (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Our 'Ask Me Another' Department (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Our Daily Sportograms (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Our Game--And Theirs (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Our Optimist Brothers (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Our Own Mr. Aesop (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Our Own Tramp Royal (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Our Uncle Samuel (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Out a Country Lane (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Out and Away (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - The Out-of-Date (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - "Out of the blight" (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Out on the Lines (Box 4, Folder 19, 21)
    - Out under the Shade (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Outbound (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Outside of Which (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Over the Beaten Trail (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Over the Border
    - Over the Christmas Trail (Box 4, Folder 18, 20)
    - Over the Hills (Box 4, Folder 7, 19, Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Over the Lost Trail (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Over the Plate (Box 4, Folder 14, Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Over the Rhine and the Rubicon (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Over the Top (Box 5, Folder 22, Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Over the Ways (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Over There (Box 5, Folder 22, Box 6, Folder 4)
    - The Overlooked Course (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Paavo Nurmi (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Paging All Poets (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - A Pair of Parades (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - The Panic in Prunes (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - The Paper from Home (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - The Parade Passes (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Parallel Cases (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Parody's Hall of Fame (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - The Party (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - The Passing (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Passing Summer (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - The Path from Arcady (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - The Path of Dreams (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - The Pathway of a Dream (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Peace for the Kaiser (Box 3, Folder 22, Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Peculiar (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - A Peep into the Dream Book (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Pelicans Win First Game (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Pen Snap Shot of the British Fan (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Pennant Muddle (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - A Pennant Phantasy (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - The Pennant Shadow (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - The People (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Percy Haughton (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Personal Liberty (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - The Phantom (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - The Phantom Corps (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Phantom Golf (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - The Phantom of Defeat (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - The Philosopher (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - A Philosophy (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - The Pick of the Lot (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Picking the Pennant Winner (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - A Picture in the Smoke (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Pictures No Artist Could Paint (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - A Pigskin Parody (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - The Pill Box (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - The Pinch Hitter (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Pirates' Massacres (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - The Pitcher's Requiem (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - A Place in the Fight (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Play off a Little Bit Farther, Old Boy (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - The Plaint of the Ages (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Players (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - The Player's Rebuttal (Box 5, Folder 11, Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Playing a Cinch Bet (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Playing Both Ends (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Playmate of the Morning (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Plea of the Weary (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - A Plea to the Winds (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - The Pleasant Drouth (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Plutonian Echoes (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - A Poet at Bay (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - The Poet Philosopher (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - The Point Being (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - A Political Hunch (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Polyrics (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Poor Little Devil (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - A Prayer (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - A Prayer for the Year's Dawn (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - A Prayer from the Field (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - A Prayer from the Line (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - A Pre-Derby Thought (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Pre-Election Prophecy (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - The Prelim's Point of Order (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - A Presidential Rebuttal (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Pretty Soon 4-23 (Box 5, Folder 3, Box 7, Folder 12)
    - The Price of Fame (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Primo Camera (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - The Primrose Way (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - The Problem on a Racing Day (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Proclamation (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - The Prodigal's Return (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Prohibition--As the Poets See It (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - The Proverbs of a Fool (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Psalm of Life (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - The Psalm of Strife (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Psalm of the 'Lid' (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Pumpelly--of Yale (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - The Punch vs. The Pen (Box 5, Folder 14, Box 6, Folder 18)
    - The Punchless Jeff (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - The Quarterback (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - The Quarterback's Prayer (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Query to Ted Ray (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Quite Different (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Quite Otherwise (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - The Race (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Rainy Days in Balldom (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - A Rambling Sporting Philosophy (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - The Rarity (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - The Rattlesnake in Rhyme (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - The Raven Speaks Again (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - The Raven Up-to-Date (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Raw Speed (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - A Ray of Light (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Real All-America (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - The Real Dark Horse (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - The Real Article (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - A Real Job for Teddy (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - The Real Springtime (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - The Real Thing (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - The Real Thing Now (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - A Reason for It (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - The Record (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - The Record Breaker (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - The Record Holder (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - The Record Upset (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Recording the Death of Baseball Slang (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - The Recruit's Dream (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - The Red Cross Stamp (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Red Roses (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - The Redhead (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - The Regular Fellow (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - The Re-Hash Club (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - The Remedy--Plus an Afterthought (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Renunciation (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Replace the Divots (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Requests Slipped to Racing Friends (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - The Requiem (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Rescued (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Resuming Where We Left Off Yesterday (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - A Retraction (Box 4, Folder 1, Box 5, Folder 30)
    - The Return (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - The Return of the D.D. (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - The Return of the Mammoths (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - The Return to Normalcy (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Returning Ball Flayers (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - The Returning Vagabond (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - The Reveille (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - The Revel (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Revenge (Box 6, Folder 5, 6)
    - A Reverie (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - The Reveries of a Napland Fan (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - The Reverse Knock (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - The Revery of an Old Wolverine (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - The Revery of an Umpire (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Revised (Box 6, Folder 25, 28)
    - The Revised City of Boston (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Revising an Old One: Cincinnati, Ohio, Sept 30
    - Revising Worn Out Maxims (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Revision (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Rex Beach (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - The Rhyme Factory (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Rhymes of the Ancient Rooter (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Rick (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - A Rift in the Dark Clouds (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - The Right Kind (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Right Weather for Work (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - The Rime of the Ancient Rooter (Box 4, Folder 4, Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Ring Lardner (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - "Ring out the old" (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - The Road to Spring (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Sks Road to the Future (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - The Road to Yesterday (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Robert Falcon Scott (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Rockne (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - "Rock me to sleep, Mother" (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Romany and Rome (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - The Rookie and the Vet (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - The Rockie and the Vet Again (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - A Rooseveltian Day (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - "Roosevelt's from out" (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Roosevelt's Soliloquy (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Rose Stahl (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Roses (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - The cough Assignment (Box 8, Folder 1, 19)
    - The Rover's Song (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Rube Marquard's Soliloquy (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - The Rube's Dream (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - The Rube's Soliloquy (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - The Ruling Classes (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - The Run of the Game (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Sad September Days (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - The Sad Sequel (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - The Saga of the Bowls (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - A Salute to Capt. Hamilton (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Saluting Prof. Evers of Chicago--and Troy (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - The Same Old Game (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Same Old Story (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Sanity Test (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Saved (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Sayings of Great Hen (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - The Scientific Way (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Scotland Robert (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Scribe's Rebuttal (Box 5, Folder 14, 30)
    - The Scrub Guard's Dream (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The Scrub's Dream (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - The Season Change (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - The Second Guess (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - The Secret of Bill's Success (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Seeger and Brooke and McRae (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Seeking Information (Box 4, Folder 25, Box 6, Folder 32)
    - The Setting Sun 5-11 (Box 6, Folder 48, Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Seven Years Ago (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - The Shadow (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - The Shaping Destiny (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - "She spoke of Alexander" (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - 'Sheath' Epics (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - The Ship of Dreams (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Short Stroll over the Hills of Sport (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - A Sign of the Times (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Signals Crossed (Box 5, Folder 1, Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Silver Cloud Ahead (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Sing On-- (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Six Years Later (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Sixteen in a Row (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Sleep, Little Fellow (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - The Slide of Paul Severe (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - The Slogan (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - The Slogan of the Day (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - The Slump Incarnate (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - The Slump of the Ages (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - A Snapshot of the City Today (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Snapshots in Styxville (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - So Clear the Road (Box 5, Folder 31)